Persona 0: Taylor, buddy. I just... Do you know what? I just knew. A few weeks ago, I said, I just feel like it's gonna happen again. Yeah. I just was like, I think she's gonna wanna do a chat.
Persona 0: I was like, we got to call Greg. We got to do something. It's been too long.
Persona 0: It has and I'm so pleased that you're up for chatting and just, just, we'll overdo your catch up.
Persona 0: Nice, it's nice. We've not oh I see what's happening now
Persona 0: the ASMR of the bread bag. Would you like to explain? Yeah, so I've been baking and so I brought Greg some sourdough because it's lemon blueberry, which I think is like a really nice variation.
Persona 0: Fantastic. Yeah. And you put the fate of Dophilia.
Persona 0: yeah you know the bread puns like i think the worst they are the better
Persona 0: What do you know what, obviously I listened to the new Heitz podcast.
Persona 0: You did? Of course not, I'm so...
Persona 0: Are you joking? Of course. So glad. And by the way, ball a move to announce an album 90 minutes into a football podcast.
Persona 0: Is that okay? No.
Persona 0: We are like, they are like weird.
Persona 0: flex but
Persona 0: Yeah, but at late 90 minutes you talked about everything and he went by the way, here's a briefcase, here's the album
Persona 0: I'm always trying to surprise people with how I announce albums. I've done a few album announcements on award shows. And so, you know, you do something one time and people are like, I know what she's going to do next. She's going to do the same things she did before. So I was like, what is, what are people not going to expect me to do is to go on a, on a football podcast and announce an album? It's very, I love the kind of polarity of the masculine feminine there.
Persona 0: Yeah, yeah.
Persona 0: as the humanity
Persona 0: Well, it's very funny, because you are very funny and you like silly stuff, essentially. And I mean, the bread, so you did your sourdough chat and then you talked about the album.
Persona 0: Yeah, I think I talked about bread for I think maybe 320 hours.
Persona 0: longer than about the record. People?
Persona 0: were like, okay, if she doesn't stop talking about sourdough, because it's like, it's a danger for me to start, because I cannot stop talking about bread when I start. And it has nothing to do with music. It's the most musically irrelevant that it's completely separate.
Persona 0: And I'm so grateful because it's got lots of cat stickers on it as well, which I've really I really like you know in the
Persona 0: chose them very carefully.
Persona 0: you um
Persona 0: for what your sense of humor is in my...
Persona 0: approximation of it. I've been known you for as long as I have.
Persona 0: That video.
Persona 0: You've nailed it. You have nailed it. By the way, when you got doing the puns of your songs and bread, you did miss Bake It Off.
Persona 0: Well that, I just thought it's too easy. No, but you like, I mean, don't feel it.
Persona 0: But that's current. That's current. It's coming, sorry. It's current. And that's the one thing that makes it relevant to our conversation. So the album's out. The album is out. And I have such.
Persona 0: Sorry.
Persona 0: uncomplicated feelings of joy about it.
Persona 0: I do not feel any twisty, tortured way about it, which is not how I felt about the last album because there was such a lag time between, you know, when you make music and then we put it out, there's often times your life can make drastic changes in those times.
Persona 0: Yes.
Persona 0: With this album, my life isn't exactly the same spot.
Persona 0: as when I wrote the record.
Persona 0: I'm so pleased to see you and I'm so pleased to see you happy as well.
Persona 0: I feel the same way about you.
Persona 0: And the album reflects your mood, which is I think you're pretty feeling quite giddy. I think you're feeling bright and happy and sweary, which I really like in some of the tracks on the album. It's just big, happy pop.
Persona 0: and you're clearly your in love.
Persona 0: yeah you are it's it's it's kind of gross
Persona 0: No, it's not.
Persona 0: It's secondingly...
Persona 0: No, it's not. It's not.
Persona 0: It's not gonna...
Persona 0: I don't know what you heard.
Persona 0: We're gonna lose!
Persona 0: It's not that kind of album.
Persona 0: No, but it's but it's lovely and bright and happy, but it's got it's got
Persona 0: But it's got teeth to it.
Persona 0: Absolutely.
Persona 0: So, I'm proud of that too, because it's a full picture of the full life experience, which for me is there's always some element of drama that someone is forcing into my consciousness, which is fun to write about too. But by the way, I love being sickringly in love. Yeah, it's so nice. It's wonderful. It's wonderful. You know, it's like I used to kind of have this dark fear that if I ever were truly like...
Persona 0: Consciousness.
Persona 0: It's so nice. It's wonderful. It's wonderful.
Persona 0: happy and free being myself and nurtured by a relationship and what happens if the writing just dries up. What if writing is directly tied to my torment and pain? And it turns out that's not the case at all. And we were just catching lightning in a bottle with this record.
Persona 0: fertilizer a
Persona 0: But it's nice because you're from a place of happiness and love. You can go back to those places. You can look forward to other things. And that's what the record feels like, is that you're still able to access those feelings of frustration, of anger, of really good stuff.
Persona 0: Yes.
Persona 0: Yeah, and you basically, like, I think, you know, I made this album with Max Martin and Shellback who I hadn't worked with in maybe seven or eight years. And in the time that we kind of took a break from working together, we were all out there honing powers of different types. And one of the things I was really playing with in our time away was writing in character and kind of developing these characters and these character arcs.